# **SURYANSH TRIPATHI**

## Computer Science

### **My Contact**

- suryanshtripathi2021@gmail.com
- +918787247275
- Noida
- in www.linkedin.com/in/suryansht ripathi
- www.suryanshtripathi.online

#### **Hard Skill**

- Full Stack Development
- HTML, CSS, Nodejs, Express
- Database Technology (MongoDB, MySQL)
- Programming Languages C, C++, Java,
   Python

#### **Soft Skill**

- Strategic planning
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Problem-solving

## **Education Background**

- 2020-2024 | Amity University
   BTech (Computer Science & Engineering)
   CGPA 8.94
- 2016-2020 | G.N National Public School PCM (Physics, Chemistry, Maths)
   S.S.C
   H.S.C

#### **About Me**

A fourth-year undergraduate student in Computer Science and Engineering. Self-motivated and a fast learner, passionate about working with tech companies and keeping up with the latest technology trends. Objectives are to build skills and gain experience through different avenues to become a change-maker.

### **Work Experience**

Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. | Summer Training 29 May 2023 - 2 July 2023

- Build a clone for the official site DISHA used by ONGC for file repo
- Learned about the IBM BPM and the designing part
- Helped portal management team in creating UI designs
- Learned about VMware by interacting with storage management team

## Amity University | In-House Practical Trainig 30 May 2022 - 10 July 2022

- Build an online food delivery website
- Main objective is to bring the restaurant services online
- Used AJAX to create asynchronous web application
- Used passport-local for the purpose of authentication
- Integrated a contact form to increase the interaction between customers and restaurant

## Google Cloud | Career Readiness Program Member *July, 2021 – Dec, 2021*

- Got an opportunity to become the part of Career Readiness Program offered by Google Cloud by completing GoogleCLoudReady Facilitator program and scoring a seat among one of the first 1000 students
- Learned all the aspects of Google Compute Engine
- Got hands-on experience with Qwiklabs on Kubernetes, BigQuery, etc.
- Got certified for completing all the 5 courses in the program

### **Certifications**

Oct 2021 Google Developer Student Clubs
30 Days of Google Cloud Program 2021

Sept 2021 Google Cloud

Architecting with Google Compute Engine Specialization.